<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>Yautja(Predator) Race</name>
	<author>Ogliss + Rebelrot</author>
	<supportedVersions>
        <li>1.0</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	<description>V1.2
	
	Requirments
	JecsTools
	Humanoid Alien Races 2.0
	
	This mod adds 
	
	Yautja(Predator) Race from the Predator film franchise to the game as a playale race.
	Pawns:
	Yautja Race (Male &amp; Female)
	
	Mechanics:
	Blooding and Marking: the Yautja value phyiscal prowess above all else, the stronger the creature they kill, the higher their social status is.
	
	Apparel:
	Yautja Thermal Webbing
	Yautja Bio Mask (Standard, Elite, Ornate Variants)
	Yautja Hunter Armour (Standard, Light, Heavy, Elite, Ornate Variants)

	Equipment:
	Yautja Gauntlet: This contains the Self Destruct Device, this item also gives the wearer a Wristblade melee attack (Thanks to LoonyLadle's Hediff Apparel Resource)
	and can also be upgraded with a Medicomp to treat the wearers wounds in the field, a Shard injector to quickly bring the wearer back to combat rediness, and a cloaking device.
	Yautja Shoulder Cannon: This item gives the wearer an automated ranged attack when active (Based on Rikki's Mining Helmet)

	Weapons: Melee
	Yautja Combistaff: can be thrown to pin enemies in place
	Bladed Maul: Simple melee weapon

	Weapons: Ranged
	Yautja Smart Disk - Research allows this to hit multiple targets while wearing a Bio Mask
	Yautja Blaster
	Yautja Needler
	Yautja Speargun - Sniper rifle equivillent
	
	incidents:
	Man in Black: using the yautja starts enables Yautji Man in Black replacer.(it will also work for other races, if they have a pawnkind with StrangerinBlack in its name)
	El Diablo: Yautji raids during Heatwaves are larger than normal.
	
	Xenomorph race from the Alien film franchise to the game as a enemy race.
	Full Xenomorph lifeycle, facehuggers can impregnate pawns, the resulting xenomorph is mostly random, however if the host is a yautja then it will always result in a predalien.
	
	Pawns:
	Queen, Drone(Spitter), Warrior, Runner, Facehugger. Chestburster, Predalien, Neomorph
	
	Mechanics:
	Acidic Blood: 
	Hidden Infections:
	
	incidents:
	They Mostly Come at Night: Xenomorph raids during the night are larger than normal
	Neomorph Spores: 
	Crashed Ship part: 
	Xenomorph Infestation: 
	
	
	
	Credits:
	C# and Xml by Ogliss
	Most Textures by Rebelrot
	Xenomorph Textures by Deon
	Xml, Balancing by Acide_Bob
	Bladed Mauled, Combistaff and Needler Textures by Temmy
	Rynath Textures by Serpy Derpy
	
	also a big Thank you to Jecrell, Erdelf, Menhi, Roolo and the many others who assited with the c#
		</description>
</ModMetaData>